All right, so this is the legends OS 2.0 walkthrough
so here on
the home page again like we still have the incorrect logos and branding because this should be a
like a like a pewter goldish black gray like that's that's the kind of the dark
mode so we need to make sure that the download Mac is functional the windows test build needs
to be functional as well so and and we need a better background here and like this needs
to be more centered it's so spread out it just doesn't look very professional
so again you know the the branding is just off with the color and the incorrect logo
so we also need to have like under the knowledge sources here we need to have like a tutorial
right here that can have the tutorial videos that show everybody how to set things up so
let's let's try atlas chat and see if this is working all right so let's take a look at this
this is very difficult to read we have a bunch of open space on both sides which doesn't really
make any sense um so but let me just ask it what to do what it can do and see what it says
okay so now it expands so this is kind of how it should always be
and then you know the live social publishing and emailing each user needs to be able to toggle that
to be active because this is kind of crazy
all right so quick action summarize today's written fireman
that's kind of cool
and like you know since this is going to be done in codex you've got the best image generation model
there is so i mean let's really create some dynamic backgrounds that are super futuristic and and really
exciting and also when we're creating this content like this we don't need all these brackets and all
this other stuff because that doesn't really make it helpful for my users all right so let's try to trigger an automation
what what automations do i have available in in 8n list them so i can choose
new lead sms alert
cool
we need to make sure of course that all of this actually works
okay so let's go back to the command center let's go to generate an image
so it's saying that the paid generation is disabled so i mean we need to be having something
oh and here are the backgrounds that i want to actually be the background for the platform
and so we've already got some images in here different headshots for people on the team
but so let's do social posts facebook warm
mixed
family borrower portrait square is good
let's see how this let's look at the advanced details all right let's generate it
all right so when i go to click generate as you can see right there there's the
you know little icon that shows that i can't actually do it so that's a problem
okay let's take a look at the email studio
the external sending needs to be enabled okay this is not for shits and giggles
and the draft over here needs to be much much smaller this needs to be the focus okay and in addition to that
the draft over here is that you know we need to have some different like
you know um prompts we also need to allow atlas to be like hey can you while we're in atlas like
hey can you draft up an email newsletter for me and template etc whatever and then just be able to be
saved and right then have it automatically be over here in the email studio that makes the most sense
and we need like you know a an ai assistant so like you know instead of like right here markdown
supported no so what we need here is like a little ai button that you can click and expand and be like hey
what topics do you want the email newsletter to be about and you can choose different topics and then it's
going to generate the email with that user's profile information all right let's take a look at the
social studio
again so n8n is connected but we've got the external publishing disabled so that needs to be corrected
and we also need that you know generate with ai and again atlas needs to be able to generate this
content for us as well and having the side a side pop out or like the little icon down here where it just
pops up and then can actually create the content and then insert it like let's do that so pick from
library let's go with this one
all right let's see if we can schedule
all right when i hit schedule it just kind of oh okay so so it does okay cool so i mean we just need it to
to be fully functional and to be able to upload you know both images and videos i just want to make sure
see videos are fine oh yeah so it does allow mp4s so that's good
so i'm uploading that all right so that worked but it'd be better if we have just uh you know a preview of it
so
all right so the calendar view for the most part looks pretty good i do want to just with all
these like fill in the space it needs to be dynamic and it needs to fill in the space
you know with with this i need to be able to
you know add
markdown files pdfs all of that stuff so for the shared resources
all right so for the settings yeah right here it needs to be able to be toggled on anything that's
disabled needs to be able to be toggled on just like how we got the toggle over here
and i mean this is where we should be able to connect our
we need to add in a n we need to add you know hey gen
you know and give people the ability to add in additional ai providers like their gemini key or
open ai or anthropic and i want them to be able to use their subscription so we need to give them the
ability to sign in with their subscription for those accounts
so i mean the admin center looks pretty good um you know i would just say
in the admin center i need to be able to like connect telegram bots or
connect you know gmail google etc like admin should have all of all of that as as well um i guess this
is the owner center but yeah
so on the add users
all right cool that works
so let me let me see if this actually does work
the admin center is going to be able to connect to the admin center
so we need that to be fixed so that was when i used this invite league share with the new user
that's what happened um i also realistically should have the ability to come in here and set you know
the password
you know um their default or i guess this should just default to like open router for the free models
the asset library good with that
so
yeah i mean
there's definitely some things that need to be fixed and we definitely need to
you know have the correct logos which like this right here
this is the legends os logo this is the correct logo that should be over here
here and everywhere that we have the legends os logo this is it and that's the branding right there okay
so i mean each user needs to be able to connect all of their
connections
so i mean i understand like owner only but we also need the users so that they can go in and connect
everything and you know having a link for them to go to
set up their n8n because i'm going to create everybody in in a in as a user
so we need to have a little guide on hey go connect your n8n connect all these credentials
because that's going to be used from you know the the social studio email etc
their calendar connections like all of that so we need to make sure that we have that stuff all in here